100dayloans.com 2012-12-18

# 100DayLoans :: Fast One Hour Loans :: Pay Day Advance Loans :: Cash Loans ::

Acquisition Media, LLC ("Acquisition Media") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the 100DayLoans.com website (the "Website"). Acquisition Media created this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy. 

This Privacy Policy applies whether you are accessing the Website via a personal computer, a mobile device or any other technology or devices now known or hereafter developed or discovered. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website and not to any websites owned by Acquisition Media's parent companies, subsidiaries or affiliates or other third-parties (collectively, "Third-Party Websites"), which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below. 

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT: (1) YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OLD, A RESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES, AND ARE OTHERWISE LEGALLY QUALIFIED TO ENTER INTO AND FORM CONTRACTS UNDER APPLICABLE LAW; AND (2) YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE. 

**TRUSTe:**

Acquisition Media has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers information collected through the Website and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile applications. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at: Attn: Legal Department, Acquisition Media, LLC, 7144 E. Stetson Dr., Suite 300, Scottsdale, AZ 85251. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here.](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

Each time you use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time you use the Website you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time you used the Website. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below. 

  **1\. U.S. GOVERNING LAW**

The Website is designed and targeted to U.S. audiences and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the U.S. Acquisition Media makes no representation that this Website is operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of, or governed by, other nations. 

If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the U.S., you access and use the Website at your own risk and initiative and you, not us, are responsible for compliance with any applicable local and national laws. By using the Website and/or providing us with your Personal Information (as defined in Section 3(e), below), you: (1) consent to the transfers and processing of any Personal Information you provide to the Website; (2) acknowledge that U.S. law provides a lower standard of protection for personal data than the laws of various countries including, but not limited to, the European Union; and (3) understand that the Website will deal with your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and U.S. law. CONSEQUENTLY, YOU HEREBY WAIVE ANY CLAIMS THAT MAY ARISE UNDER THE LAWS AND REGULATIONS THAT APPLY TO YOU IN OR OF ANY OTHER COUNTRY OR JURISDICTION. 

  **2\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Acquisition Media does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Acquisition Media obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, Acquisition Media will immediately delete such information from its database. Because Acquisition Media does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, Acquisition Media has no such information to use or disclose to third parties. 

  **3\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

(a) Traffic Data. Like most website operators, Acquisition Media automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) Internet Protocol (IP) addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Website; (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website; and (v) full Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") click stream data, including referring URLs, date and time, and content viewed or searched for on the Website (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you. 

(b) Cookies. A "Cookie" is a string of information that a website stores on a user's computer, and that the user's browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website. Acquisition Media uses "session" cookies to collect information about your use of the Website and to give you a more personalized browsing experience and help you navigate the Website more efficiently from page to page. These cookies are temporary and are deleted when you close your browser. Acquisition Media uses "persistent" cookies to gather statistical information about repeat usage from your computer or workstation. For additional information on Acquisition Media' uses of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies and Web Beacons, below. 

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY. 

(c) Web Beacons. "Web Beacons" (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to Cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access Cookies. Unlike Cookies which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, Web Beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages (or in e-mail). Web Beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. For additional information on Acquisition Media' uses of Web Beacons, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies & Web Beacons, below. 

(d) Ad Serving. Acquisition Media uses third-parties for advertising and analytics for pages that we host. These third-parties may place Cookies on your machine, use Web Beacons, gather Personal Information, gather IP addresses and log data to collect traffic and activity data in order to deliver relevant metrics, content, and advertising. The collection of this information by third-parties are subject to such third-parties' privacy policies. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below. 

(e) Personal Information. During the loan application process, you will be asked to provide Acquisition Media certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) "Identity/Contact Data" (such as your name, address, email address, social security number, driver's license or state ID number, your employer and your employer's address); (2) "Financial Information" (such as your bank, bank address, bank phone number, bank account type, length of time with your bank, your ABA routing number and your account number); (3 ) "Demographic Data" (such as your birthday, city/town, zip code, state, home ownership status, employment history, pay period frequency, next pay period and monthly income). In each case, you will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Website will not gather it surreptitiously. BY PROVIDING FINANCIAL ACCOUNT NUMBERS AND SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBERS, YOU THEREBY EXPRESSLY CONSENT THE COLLECTION BY ACQUISTION MEDIA OF SUCH INFORMATION. Acquisition Media may supplement the Personal Information you provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies, third-party service providers, etc.) who may lawfully provide such information to Acquisition Media. 

  **4\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES**

(a) Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies and Web Beacons 

Acquisition Media analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies and Web Beacons to help Acquisition Media better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Acquisition Media is able to better design the Website to improve your experience, and to serve you more relevant and interesting content and advertisements. From time to time, Acquisition Media may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies and Web Beacons in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. Acquisition Media does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies or Web Beacons to Personal Information. 

(b) Personal Information 

(i) Generally. Acquisition Media uses your Personal Information and Financial Information to identify you, to confirm facts about you, to send you information about Acquisition Media and Acquisition Media' products and services, and to contact you when necessary in connection with your use of the website. Acquisition Media uses your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies and Web Beacons, from time to time Acquisition Media may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. 

(ii) Disclosure Practices. Except under the following circumstances, Acquisition Media will keep your Personal Information private, and will not sell or otherwise share it with third parties: 

• Disclosure to Parent Companies, Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Acquisition Media discloses Personal Information to its parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates for marketing and/or administrative purposes. 

• Disclosure to Lenders. Acquisition Media refers consumers to lenders who provide short-term loans. Acquisition Media discloses Personal Information to Lenders, who use your Personal Information to identify you, to confirm facts about you, to deliver financial products and services to you, to help assess requests for financial products and services, and as necessary to service your loan. 

• Marketing Communications. Acquisition Media provides your Personal Information to third parties, so that they may contact you directly, online and offline, with information about additional products and services ("Marketing Communications"). You may opt-out of having your Personal Information provided to third parties for the purpose of Marketing Communications by clicking [here](http://www.optout-blgl.net/o-lglb-z69-85f36b03ce05b78e6817e53113984b02) and following the opt-out instructions. Even after opting-out, you may continue to receive Marketing Communications from third parties to whom Acquisition Media has already has provided your Personal Information. You will be responsible for contacting those third parties directly to request that you receive no further Marketing Communications. 

• Disclosure in Connection with Services. Acquisition Media discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide Services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as ad serving (see Section 2(d), above), email management, hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security. 

• By Law or to Protect Rights. Acquisition Media discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Acquisition Media believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Acquisition Media, third parties or the public at large. 

• Business Transfers; Bankruptcy. Acquisition Media reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Acquisition Media' assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Acquisition Media' successor organization. 

  **5\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Under California's "Shine the Light" law (CA Civil Code § 1798.83), California residents who provide personal information to businesses in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to either: (1) a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided; or (2) to be notified of a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. Acquisition Media has elected the second option. To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties, [click here](http://www.optout-blgl.net/o-lglb-z69-85f36b03ce05b78e6817e53113984b02) and follow the opt-out instructions. 

  **6\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

The security of your personal information is important to us; Acquisition Media has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of your Personal Information. When you enter sensitive on our registration forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

  **7\. EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS; MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS**

By completing an application through the Website, you consent to receive certain administrative email communications from Acquisition Media. You also consent to receive periodic online and offline marketing communications from Acquisition Media. You may opt-out of receiving Acquisition Media marketing communications at any time by clicking [here](http://www.optout-blgl.net/o-lglb-z69-85f36b03ce05b78e6817e53113984b02) and following the opt-out instructions. 

  **8\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You represent and warrant that all information you provide on any application form or otherwise in connection with your use of the Website will be complete and accurate. To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, your Personal Information, please email Acquisition Media at legal@blueglobalmedia.com. 

  **9\. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES**

Acquisition Media neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by Acquisition Media. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to a Third-Party Website, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect your privacy. 

  **10\. DATA RETENTION**

We will retain and use your Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. 

  **11\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any change in how we use your Personal Information we will notify you by means of a notice on this Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

Effective Date: February 7, 2012 

Acquisition Media, LLC  
7144 E. Stetson Drive, Suite 300  
Scottsdale, AZ 85251  
legal@blueglobalmedia.com 

100DayLoans offers simple easy short term loans with no Faxing Required. Apply today and get a bigger payday Loan. You can use our cash advance loans to catch up on bills and avoid costly NSF and late fees.
